Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 19
How far are you going to go?
No matter where we go, we don't need that stuff. It'll just be me and you.
Let's just pretend that stuff doesn't exist for a bit, okay?
Don't go too far.
Keep your mouth shut. Don't even let out a peep.
Eun Jo will keep her mouth closed.
Do you know that I'm hungry?
I haven't eaten a single meal since I got taken away.
Not even one meal?
I was afraid of getting poisoned. How could I have eaten? I was too scared.
I don't know why I feel hungry whenever I see your face.
Look straight ahead. Instead of smiling.
I'm not smiling because I plan to eat your flesh, so don't worry.
What?
You look like skin and bones, so what would I eat?
You still can laugh?
Yes.
There are no restaurants. How could you come to such a place?
You didn't listen and just kept driving. You're hungry. What are we going to do?
It's okay. Come here, let's talk for a while.
Where are you going?
Grandmother.
Hi, Grandmother.
I know this isn't a restaurant,
but would you be able to give us something to eat?
There's nothing around here, and there's someone who hasn't eaten for days.
If he suddenly eats just anything, he might get sick.
Would you be able to please cook us some porridge?
Just plain rice porridge would be fine.
I'll pay you well for the meal.
You little punk, remember this.
I know what thoughts are going around in your head right now,
but we agreed to pretend nothing happened for a bit.
At this moment, we're back in time in the month of May, year 2002. Got it?
Starting right now, for one hour and 20 minutes, every ten minutes is one year, got it?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I didn't take the train, and I've been living with you at Dae Seong True Winemakers the whole time.
Starting now!
Starting now, it'll be the year 2002 for ten minutes.
Eun Jo, you little punk.
Problem number 10 on your Math homework. Why did you get it wrong?
Didn't I show you a problem that was almost exactly the same?
This won't do. You need to get your hands hit. Stretch out your hands.
You won't? Do you find your teacher funny?
Just eat your porridge.
Please.
(T/N: Adding a formal ending to her sentence instead of using informal speech.)
You've been spending a lot of time with that music major these days.
Who is that punk? Oh, you're smiling?
You little... you're smiling? You smile instead of answering me?
At 4:30 p.m., I was in the year 2005.
I was a new student at the university this person was studying at after he returned to school.
This person was my college senior, who helped me carry my bag everyday.
Last Stop Store
Grandmother, can we leave our car with you as a guarantee and borrow your bicycle?
Even though you're smart, you're doomed if you don't study.
Do you know how picky your professor is?
4:40 p.m., it's the year 2006.
After this person graduated, he postponed job hunting, and pursued postgraduate education.
Because without him around school, he was afraid that I'd decide to start dating
so he wanted to keep an eye on me.
GPA? You call that a GPA? 3.8?
Is that even a GPA?
I've never considered anything under 4.0 a real GPA.
Studying overseas? You think I'd let you go?
I don't even let you go to another nearby neighborhood alone
because I'm scared someone will snatch you away.
What? You want to go to America to study?
Until I graduate, just learn English from me for the time being.
Repeat after me. "I am a boy."
5:00 p.m., it's 2008.
I've graduated from college. Even until now,
this person and I haven't broken up once.
Do you make sounds when you smile too?
Smile one more time. Huh?
What? Move aside.
I told you to smile one more time. It's fascinating.
It's all full now.
Yes.
Smile, you punk! While making a sound!
Try looking around and see if you can find a guy like me.
I'm handsome, intelligent, have ability, and a sense of humor.
Although I don't have money, that can be earned in the future.
There are so many married couples who start out with just two spoons and bowls.
The one thing I feel sorry for is making you take care of my father right after we got married.
After my father stepped down from the company,
he completely became a toothless tiger.
It's not bad. Control lies in our hands now.
2010, 5:20 p.m.
This person finally found a job.
He didn't do anything wrong all this time,
so he didn't feel any guilt inside at all.
He proposed to me, without any burden.
I didn't agree right away,
I told him to give me some time to think, just to make things hard for him.
Go and take it back. I'll start the car up.
How do you expect to get married with nothing but a set of utensils?
Let's think about it after we've saved up some money.
Right now...not a chance.
Thanks for lending it to us, Grandma. Thank you.
♫ Leaving behind the time ♫
♫ which was buried in my heart ♫
Eun Jo. I know what kind of girl you are, that's why I'm doing this.
I'm going to give these documents to Hong Joo Ga.
If you don't want to give up Dae Seong True Winemakers, there's no other way.
- Come back immediately.
- Go home.
I'll take care of everything.
I said come back right away!
Eun Jo, listen to what I'm saying. Let's save the winery.
Once we've saved the winery somehow,
even if I become a beggar walking the streets barefoot, I would not care.
Do you think I'll let you make that kind of a deal?
Will doing this really ease your guilt?
Are you that kind of person?
I don't expect to ease my guilt.
♫ Will you who knows everything about me ♫
How could I ever be at ease?
The fourth thing I haven't told you yet...
I'll tell you after everything is over. Wait for me.
Hello? Hello?!
♫ The day I return to your side again ♫
♫ will come again ♫
Goo Hyo Seon
Hello?
Unni.
Joon Soo has disappeared.
What did you say?
I went to find him because he was supposed to have come back from kindergarten already,
but they said he had already left.
I even tried contacting all of Joon Soo's friends,
but they all said they didn't see him.
I looked all over the neighborhood and the house...
Unni, what should we do?
Where are you? I'm scared to death...
Hurry home.
Hey kids, do you know where Joon Soo is?
We don't know.
- Joon Soo!
- Child!
Joon Soo!
Joon Soo! Joon Soo!
Child!
Joon Soo. Joon Soo!
Joon Soo!
My fairy tale ended at 5:20.
The recipient's phone is turned off, so you will be connected to voice mail.
After you've been connected, the phone charges will begin.
Mom.
Stop crying and get up. Your mom will be in pain if she sees you like this.
Ahjumma, I'm always so upset every day.
I hate when the ajusshis make fun of my mom,
and I also hate it when my mom smiles at the ajusshis.
I hate it when Mom fights with the ajusshis too.
I hate everything so much.
Child, you think your mom does those things because she likes it?
You think she goes around pouring wine and smiling because she likes it?
She does it because she wants to feed and support you.
Why are you hiding and crying all the time when you don't know the truth?
- Hurry and get up.
- Ajumma, you don't even know anything!
Do you know who the ajusshi my mom is drinking with is?
He's my deskmate's father.
She already hates me so much,
and teases me a lot.
You're really that upset?
You're really upset?
I'm sorry.
Who would've known it would be this painful,
and that a young child would shed so much blood and tears?
I'm sorry.
Joon Soo...
What if something bad happened?
No, that won't happen.
Why are you thinking that? We'll find Joon Soo.
We've reported it already, so the police will go out and help find him.
We also haven't gone to all the houses of Joon Soo's friends yet.
What's with you? Where have you been all day?
I'll tell you later.
- Right now, we should go find Joon Soo...
- I was pacing around the whole day.
Even though I kneeled outside Halmoni's house, she wouldn't even take a look at me.
No matter what I said, she wouldn't even listen.
When I got back home, Joon Soo wasn't there.
As time passed while I went to find him,
I was so anxious that I couldn't take it anymore.
Where were you? What were you doing?
I'll tell you later. Let's keep looking for Joon Soo for now.
Are you even worried about Joon Soo?
Are you seriously saying that right now?
Have you ever hugged Joon Soo?
Do you even know that Joon Soo is our younger brother?
Have you ever considered him your younger brother?
Sometimes ... I really can't
understand you.
Sunshine Class - Goo Joon Soo
Sunshine Class - Goo Joon Soo]
Dad
[Dad, Mom, Little Noona, Me]
Evil witch!
Hong Joo Ga
I've brought a memorandum promising not to touch the shares of Dae Seong True Winemakers,
After you've given back the shares you've already gotten, contact me, Hyung.
Then I'll give you the documents I have.
I'll be waiting for you to contact me, Hyung. You know I can't wait long, right?
I'll wait until tomorrow morning.
I don't need any of that. You said you'll do it?
Do it then. The day you cause chaos with those documents
you know what will happen to Dad, right?
Knowing that, you're still going to do it?
You can't.
Just watch whether I'll do it or not, Hyung.
What?
I will wait until tomorrow morning.
Hey. What do you mean Joon Soo disappeared?
What is that supposed to mean, guys?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
There are so many people in the house! How could you have not taken care of him properly?!
Lower your voice, Mom.
Did you search carefully?
Have you tried looking? Have you searched properly?
Have you looked everywhere? Have you tried looking everywhere possible?
Are you back now?
Are you back for good?
Joon Soo!
Joon Soo! Joon Soo, come here.
- It's Mom. Mom's here.
- Mom!
Joon Soo.
Stop, stop. Mom's here. Stop crying.
It's okay, Mom's here. Mom's here. Stop crying, stop.
Oh my baby, my baby.
Stop crying. Mom's here.
It's okay, it's okay. Poor child.
Close the door... Jeong Woo.
Our fairytale ended at 5:20 p.m.
Joon Soo. Why did you go in there?
Why did you go under the desk, Joon Soo?
Hide and seek.
Hide and seek?
With whom? Who were you playing hide and seek with?
Joon Soo, who were you playing hide and seek with?
Were you playing hide and seek with the kitchen grandmother?
♪ Hide, hide carefully. I can see your hair! ♪
I'm going to look now!
Joon Soo, you rascal! You rascal!
You beautiful little rascal! You beautiful little rascal!
♪ Hide carefully. I can see your hair! ♪
You little rascal.
Stay still. Stay still.
Does this tickle? It tickles, doesn't it? You little rascal!
You, you, you.
Aigoo, that's enough.
That's enough. That's enough.
Aren't you sleepy? Sleep for a bit. Close your eyes.
Aigoo. Such a good boy, you lovely brat.
Aigoo, you, you, you, you, you naughty rascal.
You, you, you, you, you naughty and beautiful rascal!
You, you, you, you, you!
You must have been bored all this time, haven't you?
After you get a nice sleep like a good little boy...
Mom will come and play with you all the time.
Joon Soo, now
you have to take care of Mom and your noona's for me.
Now...
you have to protect those pitiful women.
Okay?
Yes.
Good boy.
You stupid brat.
Stupid brat... but you're still my good boy.
What are you looking at just sitting there?
Even if you have something to say, keep your mouths shut and go get some sleep.
Because I have nothing to say.
You really have nothing to say, Mom?
Nothing.
You really have nothing to say?
I said I don't. Even if I did I wouldn't say it.
I'm tired. I want to lie down, so you girls leave.
I'm hungry.
I'm so hungry that I could faint.
Give me food. Please make me food.
Did you know?
Hyo Seon can't taste anything.
Whether it's salty as sumac or bland as tofu,
everything tastes the same to Hyo Seon.
She's still like that?
We took her to the hospital, but they couldn't find the reason.
You're the one who caused it. What were you thinking?
What were you thinking when you left, and what were you thinking when you came back?
Are you going to leave again? You are, right?
Did you come back because you think there's something worth taking?
The food is ready. If Hyo Seon is sleeping, wake her up.
Eat slowly. Slowly.
No one's going to steal away your food so eat slowly.
I said eat slowly!
What are you doing? Drink water.
Mom, we are completely broke now.
We might even have to give up this house.
What?
It's possible that we might be left with nothing.
I'm not sure what it means to be left with nothing,
But Mom if we're left with nothing in this house,
we won't be family anymore, right?
What do you mean?
What do you mean we're giving up this house? Why?
I...
What... are you going to do with me?
I'd be good to know beforehand.
That way I can ask for a loan.
I can't die just because I'm left alone.
Instead of disappearing without a word all of a sudden,
can you warn me before you disappear again, Mom?
I can't say these kinds of things, so ask Eun Jo.
She's never heard me say anything sweet to her before, not even once.
I couldn't do that at all to her, but I did it to you so much that it drove me crazy.
As you already know, I felt like I could make a meal out of you,
so I spoke with sugar in my mouth. Yes, I wasn't sincere.
If I start talking to you sweetly right now, will you believe me?
Will you believe me?
Just keep eating.
You eat too.
And I don't know what she's talking about. Just ask her calmly.
My head hurts so much that I can't ask her myself.
But, you...
Why does she speak so incoherently?
What is she talking about? There's no beginning or end.
If we need to give this house up because of whatever reason,
then we could figure out how to stop it.
She first asks if I'm going to abandon her?
You should learn how to talk from Eun Jo.
That's not the problem now though. It's this house.
Give up this house?
Do you think I'll watch this house fall into someone else's hands?
I'm Song Kang Sook! We're definitely not giving it up.
Keep that in mind and get back to your food.
Chew carefully and slowly.
Just because I was away from the house for a few days, you've let it get to this state?
Look here, all of you.
If you're going to do a half-hearted job and gloss things over just because the President is no longer here,
pack your bags and leave this house immediately!
Those who are not working hard or slacking, I've got my eye on you already.
Did you think I wouldn't know who was being lazy?
Look here, Hyo Seon's Uncle!
Why are you here at this time? Why are you at home leaving the winery empty?
If you're lazy, it won't matter if you're her uncle or the dog's uncle, I'll kick you out right away.
Get back to work immediately!
Hey, are you going to wear that?
Why? I shouldn't?
If you dress so plainly, avoid going with me. I'll be the one more embarrassed.
This won't do. Move aside and let me see.
But, why are you doing this? Where are we going?
Hey you, all of these clothes... Give some of these clothes to Eun Jo.
You always wear such pretty and expensive clothes.
Don't you feel bad to see the way Eun Jo dresses?
This one, this one and also this one...
And this. Give all these ones to Eun Jo.
What are you looking at?
I'm your stepmother. I'm doing this because I'm trying to act like your stepmother.
What... What did you say?
Take that off and put this on. This matches your skin tone.
T- trying to act like my stepmother?
You know, I thought this over.
Whether or not you agree with me, like me or hate me...
none of it matters.
I really can't tell a lie, even if I died and came back to life.
And speaking sugary words
I can't do that anymore either.
Hyo Seon.
If I have to think of you the same way I think of Eun Jo or Joon Soo,
my insides would explode and I would die.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
How can you be the same as Eun Jo or Joon Soo?
When I didn't even give birth to you. You know that much, right?
Of course you're different.
If Eun Jo or Joon Soo got an illness,
it'd hurt like I lost a part of me inside.
If you got sick, it wouldn't hurt like that.
Even though it wouldn't feel like I lost a part of me,
it would at least hurt like I got cut by a knife.
Somehow, I've been trying to live my life...
But, there's no one else who reminds me of your father more than you do. You're the only one.
Let's live like that. I'm your stepmother, and you're my stepdaughter.
If you keep that much in mind, you won't hope for anything more.
If there was nothing more you hope for, why would the two of us need to fight like wild dogs?
Isn't that so?
If I'm wrong in what I said, tell me so.
Do you really mean what you said about hurting and bleeding like getting cut by a knife?
That's right.
Do I really mean that much to you?
Yes, you do.
We don't have time so hurry up and change your clothes.
As time goes by...
Even if it takes a little more time..
When I'm also sick,
will you feel like you lost a part of you inside?
Hey, to that extent, that's considered a threat.
Would you like it if I put sugar in mouth to say sweet lies to you?
Even if not to the point of feeling like you lost a part of you,
Then... Even so, do you think it would hurt you like something similar?
Do you think it will hurt you in a similar way?
Well, that depends on how you behave.
You're not going to change?
If it depends on me, if I am good,
will it hurt you in a similar way? Will it?
Hey, why are you trying to see me hurt, anyway?
What else in the world am I supposed to say now?!
- Why are you being so bothersome?!
- Mom...
Don't forget that you owe me.
Don't forget about the sins you committed against me and Dad.
I'm not going to ask you to make it up to me some other way.
So please hurt for me in a similar way like you do for Unni, Mom.
Song Eun Jo is forever Han Jeong Woo's woman
♫ Leaving behind the time ♫
I can't let you go alone!
Noona, you're... my woman. I love you! I love you!
♫ and I waited for you ♫
You don't know me?
Noona, no matter where you are or how you're living,
I'm going to find you and take care of you.
Just trust in me!
♫ Looking only in this direction, my two eyes ♫
♫ can't say they waited for you ♫
♫ I can't say I'm coming back ♫
- Santa Lucia-
- Hey, stop that.
♫ who cannot forget you ♫
- O sole mio...
- You...
♫ If there are tens of thousand who will just love you ♫
♫ If I can always look at you ♫
♫ The day I return to your side again ♫
♫ will come again ♫
Noona. I have something to say to you.
Jeong Woo, not right now. Later.
I can't wait. It has to be now.
Song Eun Jo is forever Han Jeong Woo's woman
I know what you're going to say.
What are you talking about?
I'm definitely going to be rejected. I know that already.
Even so, I'm going to do it.
No matter how you respond, I'm still going to ask you.
Since you were 14 years old, you've been my woman.
I'm not going to cause tears to fall from your eyes.
I'm not going to let you go hungry for food.
And whatever you wanted to be, I would make it happen for you.
Not another man, but I... wanted to be the one to do all this for you in order to win your heart.
Jeong Woo.
I can't watch you rotting here anymore.
If you were living your life here smiling,
if you were in a loving relationship with Hong Gi Hoon
then what could I say?
That Hong Gi Hoon has only made you cry. It'll be like that in the future too.
I cannot stand to see that.
- Jeong Woo.
-Live with me.
- Live with me.
Live with me. Live with me, you brat!
I'll make you happy.
I'll live having only eyes for you for the rest of my life. I'll live for you.
As long as I have you, I can do anything.
Jeong Woo.
Jeong Woo, I... like that person.
It's not because I don't like you,
but it's because I like that person too much, so I can't live with you.
I'm not even sure whether I can spend my life with that person,
but even if I can't...
Even if we are not meant to be together forever...
I wonder if that even matters.
What does it matter? When I love him to death.
A girl who likes you just as much as I like that person
will definitely appear.
It'll definitely happen, Jeong Woo.
Because you're a good kid.
I have to go to that person right now.
That person might lose his father.
I care for you. You're so lovely.
Because you're by my side, I feel safe, Jeong Woo.
Eun Jo.
Incoming call
...
Hello?
Stop right there. Don't take another step.
Where are you?
Stop right there! Right where you are!
Eun Jo. Don't do this.
It'll be over soon. It'll be over very soon.
- It's already over.
- What do you mean?
I ran here because I thought you might be doing more useless negotiations.
What do you mean it's over?
The prosecutors' office have laid charges against Hong Joo Ga and Chairman Hong Han Seok.
What did you say?
Good job. You won.
Do you know Park Ki Man, Hong Joo Ga's former Headquarters Director?
He reported Hong Joo Ga and Chairman Hong to the prosecutors' office
and made a declaration of conscience this morning.
You should've picked up your phone! You should've discussed it with me. Why are you doing things alone?
It seems he needs to report to the prosecutors' office. Are you sure you don't want to go see him?
Open the window for a moment. Open the window for a moment, please!
I'll ask you this, one more time.
Can't you just give everything up?
Just give everything up and free yourself.
I'll take care of you. I'll earn money with my own hands
and support you financially.
We'll play Go together and go fishing.
I'll be a good son to you.
Please give everything up and emerge from all this, Father.
Let's go.
Nan Hee!
Hyo Seon!
You remember my mom, right?
Hello.
We need hiking outfits for a group. Can you show us?
A group? Of course. This way please.
Who is it for?
Who else? I'm buying it for Eun Jo. Why?
Don't play favorites. I'm also Dad's daughter.
We'll take this too.
It's pretty, right?
From the start, this wasn't supposed to happen.
You should've told me right from the start.
Things would've been better if you had told me when you were suffering.
If we discussed things together nicely,
maybe neither of us
would've had to lose anything.
Why did you do that?
You shouldn't have.
You can rely on me. When Dad said this to me,
although I didn't have any expectations right away,
at least I knew there was someone I could rely on one day.
At that time,
I felt the part of me that was tightly bound together
slowly opening up.
Lean on me.
You can lean on me.
This time, you can lean on me.
Okay?
♫ Again today my memory led me astray ♫
♫ I who am strolling at the end of the street ♫
♫ where you can't hold me again ♫
♫ I ask again about the way ♫
♫ While looking at heaven I'm praying ♫
While looking at heaven I'm praying
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I can't do without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫ because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
♫ My bruised heart ♫
♫ is shouting so that ♫
♫ I can find you ♫
♫ Wherever you are ♫
♫ Can't you hear my voice? ♫
♫ Come to me ♫
♫ Even if I live again ♫
♫ No matter how many times I am reborn ♫
♫ There isn't a day that I can live without you. ♫
♫ The love I will protect ♫
♫ The love I love ♫
I was always afraid of the things I had to deal with.
Now, I'm not afraid of anything.
I can't believe you. What are you guys plotting?
I'm coming to you now, my stupid brat.
Song Eun Jo is forever Han Jeong Woo's woman
No matter where you are, I'll be with you. You know that, right?.
I could just leave like that.
Unni abandoned me and left.